itty.bz 2011-11-26

# itty.bz

Itty.bz strongly believes in a consumer's right to privacy. itty.bz does not engage in the collection, distribution, sale or use of personally identifiable information about Web Users, such as email address, name, phone number and street address. All web user data collected by itty.bz as part of the ad serving process is not personally identifiable (browser type, for example) and is used in aggregate form. itty.bz does not know your email address. itty.bz does not conduct individual web user "profiling".

Advertisers using the itty.bz Network may collect personally identifiable information explicitly provided by consumers for purposes including the purchase of goods and services, order shipment, and sweepstakes entry. Personally identifiable information collected by Advertisers using the itty.bz Network is subject to the privacy policies of the individual advertisers.

## technology

Itty.bz uses a feature of Internet browsers called a "cookie". Cookies are files that the Internet browser places on your computer's hard drive. itty.bz also uses "web beacons", also known as clear gif technology, or action tags. Web beacons are tiny colorless image files placed in a web page, which are served by itty.bz and counted when served. Web beacons are used to track the completion of transactions and submittal of applications.

Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements. Cookies are not viruses and cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer. Cookies are used to ensure that when a web user clicks on an ad, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. They are also used by our reporting system to estimate the total reach of an ad campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies are also used to control the delivery of a series of ads to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement.

There are many misconceptions about cookies and web beacons, some of which we will try to clarify. Cookies and web beacons do not tell us an e-mail address or any other personally identifiable information. itty.bz does not and cannot use cookies or web beacons to retrieve personal information from your computer.

Web Users have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in their browser. Please see your browser supplier's website for details on how to do this.

## information collection and use

As part of our on-going efforts to ensure the best possible experience for all recipients of itty.bz advertising, we use cookies and web beacons to collect data from browsers to aggregate statistical information. This includes IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of itty.bz. itty.bz does not, and cannot collect personal information.

Advertisements delivered by itty.bz may let you gain access to other sites. The linked sites are not under the control of itty.bz. itty.bz does not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services and content of linked sites. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
